

KANIJ FATEMA

CONTACT

Bē behance.net/kanijkoli

m kanijkoli.github.io/portfolio

Mohammadpur, Dhaka

01732031140

🔀 kanijkoli098@gmail.com

About Me

I have UI/UX design experience and specialization in complex web and mobile app design. I have a reputation for being a strong team player and multitasker and working hard, pick things up quickly.

Skills

Figma

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, XD

MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

JavaScript

Flutter

REFERENCES

Kabir Hossen

Finance Manager, Marcan Pharmaceuticals Canada Inc.

Email: kabirhossenacca@gmail.com

Cell: +1 613 6180705

Shanto Islam

Lead UI UX Designer, Zaimah Technologies LTD

Email: pavelshanto30@gmail.com

Cell: + 880 1686830577



EDUCATION

Master's in CSE

Jahangirnagar University

Bachelor's in CSE

Gono University

May 2017 - October 2021

May 2022 - Present



WORK EXPERIENCE

Flutter Developer

October 2021 to January 2022

DivineITLtd

Internship

Responsibilities:

- Create an online-based "Food Delivery App" using Adobe XD
- Create app with Dart and Rest API

Associate UI UX Designer

July 2022 to August 2022

Zaimah Technologies Limited

Full Time

Responsibilities:

- Wireframing and Prototyping
- Graphics Design, Interaction Design
- Task Analysis, Content Analysis, Task Flows
- Integrate new graphics concepts and interfaces
- Collaborate with design teams to develop, testing
- Usability Testing, User Journey, Experience Strategy
- Identified and resolved flaws, User research and Analysis
- Proposed new idea for improving User experience by researching

Tools: Figma, Adobe Illustrator

Key Project:

Worked with the design team to create a new POS system, resulting in useful for every pharmacy and for the medicine supplier.



PERSONAL PROJECT

Library Web Design

- Design a useful and elegant digital experience of Library for user.
- Implemented UX strategies.
- Create Wireframe, Case Study, Mockup and Prototype.

Library Dashboard Design

- An account overview with current products.
- Usage statistics for the day to year, including total books, users, borrowed books, overdue books, requested books, unique visitors, and visitors by age.
- A list of active features with a brief description of each.
- Create Mockup, Dark mode and Light mode.

Restaurant Booking Web Design

- Design a useful Restaurant booking website for user
- Create Case Study, Mockup and Prototype.
- Create Wireframe, Case Study, Mockup and Prototype.